Fake Cops. Real Trouble.
Let's Be Cops is a comedy film directed by Luke Greenfield.
Best pals Ryan and Justin are stalled in their respective careers -- a fact
that is painfully driven home when they go to a college reunion.
Dressed as police in the mistaken belief that they were to attend a costume party, Ryan
and Justin find that the uniforms earn them much respect and attention.
Although Justin is uncomfortable with the idea, Ryan decides to continue with the
charade, putting them both in increasingly dangerous situations.
When these newly-minted “heroes” get tangled in a real life web of mobsters and
dirty detectives, they must put their fake badges on the line.
Ryan Davis, played by Jake Johnson.
Justin Chang, played by Damon Wayans Jr..
Officer Segars, played by Rob Riggle.
Josie, played by Nina Dobrev.
Mossi, played by James D'Arcy.
Pupa, played by Keegan-Michael Key.
Let's Be Cops is a 2014 American buddy cop action comedy film
co-written and directed by Luke Greenfield.
The film stars Damon Wayans Jr.
and Jake Johnson as two friends who pretend to be
police officers in Los Angeles.
The film co-starred Nina Dobrev, Rob Riggle, James D'Arcy, and Andy García.
It was filmed on location in Atlanta, Georgia, and released on August 13, 2014.
It received negative reviews from critics and grossed $138.2 million
worldwide against a production budget of $17 million.
The film explores themes of robbery, corruption, police, kidnapping, nightclub.
The tone is lighthearted.